{
  "-JO3cycqqTXDNF7HNTeX" : {
    "Answer" : "*reified ",
    "Question" : "Do you feel ownership of your body?"
  },
  "-JO7DtWOkStgnL7LimoZ" : {
    "Answer" : "thedish ",
    "Question" : "What is your favorite news source?"
  },
  "-JO7DXu6ugyCOOj2bS83" : {
    "Answer" : "6",
    "Question" : "On a scale of 1-10, rate your current happiness."
  },
  "-JO3c-YcJBam4hXAg1xM" : {
    "Answer" : "$$$",
    "Question" : "Are deadlines of relative, rather than absolute, importance to you?"
  },
  "-JO2z-Gbh8c990wYTMps" : {
    "Answer" : "Ok",
    "Question" : ""
  },
  "-JO7DT1yxG-1PXQIU_SD" : {
    "Answer" : "often",
    "Question" : "How often do you express affection to loved ones?"
  },
  "-JO3dZxR6uq8yc8jWEgw" : {
    "Answer" : "enough ",
    "Question" : "To what degree do you think your local geography influences your aesthetic preferences?"
  },
  "-JO7E5DzztvxrkBDPmsg" : {
    "Answer" : "false",
    "Question" : "No surprises is better than surprises. True or false."
  },
  "-JO7Dc_sM_toap48UWDl" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy being in large groups?"
  },
  "-JO7EQrFlFcsMIhIrTjd" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you make an effort to look smart?"
  },
  "-JO7EhBYheo9XymZBOge" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Have you ever wished you were an inanimate object?"
  },
  "-JO3azpqzQKZZtrB27Kf" : {
    "Answer" : "nah",
    "Question" : "Do you feel stressed or guilty at not having accomplished enough?"
  },
  "-JO7EUMHmT2FzSYd-iY3" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you feel ownership of your body?"
  },
  "-JO3bySq9hbmnRiXzEq2" : {
    "Answer" : "hi Kei",
    "Question" : "Describe the latest email or text message you've received."
  },
  "-JO7E9QnGEgfr1Iji-Tc" : {
    "Answer" : "no",
    "Question" : "Are your computer desktop and file system usually neat and orderly?"
  },
  "-JO3davx2pKxfh1pCXNO" : {
    "Answer" : "$$$",
    "Question" : "Do you use others' accounts on media streaming services?"
  },
  "-JO2ee1jVZCuNy8l3e3v" : {
    "Answer" : "Kind of",
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy the outdoors?"
  },
  "-JO3aeFywOF1e-CGRKXF" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you spend a lot of your free time learning about things which have absolutely no practical application?"
  },
  "-JO3aiGWzhgdxX-EelOb" : {
    "Answer" : "capitalism ",
    "Question" : "What do you feel is the biggest problem in the world today?"
  },
  "-JO3dI7LHfGKXPP3QqZ2" : {
    "Answer" : "absolutely ",
    "Question" : "If you found yourself in a position of absolute power, would you set limitations on exercising it?"
  },
  "-JO7EJppMo_d9V8z5mLI" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Are there perfect objects?"
  },
  "-JO7E8DTjrghceZjSZ58" : {
    "Answer" : "no i dont think so ",
    "Question" : "Have you ever written a review on Yelp? If yes, why?"
  },
  "-JO7DWKh7mK6Vlu9oj60" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you feel secure?"
  },
  "-JO7EL3a1DArErP3wgG8" : {
    "Answer" : "rarely",
    "Question" : "How often do you change your sheets?"
  },
  "-JO3cg7jZsYOzI9Ix-mG" : {
    "Answer" : "objective c was an inside job ",
    "Question" : "What conspiracy theories do you believe?"
  },
  "-JO7Eu11kMAfarVz1pKd" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you feel confident in your answers here?"
  },
  "-JO7Et0rk6k1Ofx4aW_W" : {
    "Answer" : "8 or nine ",
    "Question" : "What is the average number of tabs you have open at any given time?"
  },
  "-JO3cMtELIK_PRuFqpva" : {
    "Answer" : "\"to be\"?",
    "Question" : "In your next birth, you would love to be:"
  },
  "-JO3brGvZpkIr2uv-Wbz" : {
    "Answer" : "idiomatically ",
    "Question" : "Do you take failure in stride?"
  },
  "-JO3cSh9QB15Q2GbsBxg" : {
    "Answer" : "same as it ever was",
    "Question" : "Is time running out, slowing down, or changed completely?"
  },
  "-JO3b570Ni9YCSv-alwv" : {
    "Answer" : "ASCII",
    "Question" : "Describe what this looks like to you: (8>/--<"
  },
  "-JO3cGjCvtEZFAIlVWAb" : {
    "Answer" : "We so often are ",
    "Question" : "Have you ever wished you were an inanimate object?"
  },
  "-JO3blzGglxU5TRIXpXr" : {
    "Answer" : "critique of pure tolerance ",
    "Question" : "Do you value justice higher than mercy?"
  },
  "-JO7DbRfn7nCbSZ5a0ke" : {
    "Answer" : "my network",
    "Question" : "What makes you feel optimistic?"
  },
  "-JO7Do3kV4M_eJtOobwo" : {
    "Answer" : "not sure",
    "Question" : "Do you value justice higher than mercy?"
  },
  "-JO3axKCAWZQ3JQHv2EF" : {
    "Answer" : "direct observation ",
    "Question" : "What is your favorite news source?"
  },
  "-JO3_Zm_opdr2TViVJV9" : {
    "Answer" : "6",
    "Question" : "On a scale of 1-10, rate your current happiness."
  },
  "-JO2eg1OZsMrAF690a5j" : {
    "Answer" : "Not very",
    "Question" : "How often do you express affection to loved ones?"
  },
  "-JO3cYBgLfJ-sj2cacuB" : {
    "Answer" : "n+1",
    "Question" : "What is the average number of tabs you have open at any given time?"
  },
  "-JO7EkijUEimIBIGT03M" : {
    "Answer" : "not sure",
    "Question" : "\"Remember those quiet evenings.\" Have you seen this before?"
  },
  "-JO7DyUaz2wNCayiJdUb" : {
    "Answer" : "ive never failed at anything",
    "Question" : "Do you take failure in stride?"
  },
  "-JO7EV_t7vcu_3P0ALdG" : {
    "Answer" : "no",
    "Question" : "Does your right hand look unusual now?"
  },
  "-JO3bD-ZQ1FrQ_o0gCDa" : {
    "Answer" : "Some grammar is better than other",
    "Question" : "No surprises is better than surprises. True or false."
  },
  "-JO3d4mdEZJIMDkVYRr1" : {
    "Answer" : "russian dolls",
    "Question" : "What would your ideal phone case look like?"
  },
  "-JO7E1TVNrXdDqM4aQOk" : {
    "Answer" : "km chee",
    "Question" : "Describe something you like."
  },
  "-JO7EMCCSYNXVTCzxzM3" : {
    "Answer" : "yes. daily",
    "Question" : "Do you worry about the NSA reading your email? If yes, how frequent is your worry?"
  },
  "-JO3dYPIta0PHxi8b9_p" : {
    "Answer" : "enough ",
    "Question" : "How many piano tuners are there in the entire world?"
  },
  "-JO7DRS-vzbCfQpnoDND" : {
    "Answer" : "ok\n",
    "Question" : ""
  },
  "-JO7EmizfituwBmAazlP" : {
    "Answer" : "probably at first",
    "Question" : "If you found yourself in a position of absolute power, would you set limitations on exercising it?"
  },
  "-JO3__fphtz4Oqu3883b" : {
    "Answer" : "nah",
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy the outdoors?"
  },
  "-JO2z28x8J73PUgWSMla" : {
    "Answer" : "Not too long",
    "Question" : "When was the last time you went for a walk?"
  },
  "-JO7DvzUxyziBnrdtzDm" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you feel stressed or guilty at not having accomplished enough?"
  },
  "-JO3ctlBhxzkoQOC3Iv6" : {
    "Answer" : "of course ",
    "Question" : "Do you feel confident in your answers here?"
  },
  "-JO3cCwYLqjuTVFLPFnC" : {
    "Answer" : "Have you?",
    "Question" : "\"Remember those quiet evenings.\" Have you seen this before?"
  },
  "-JO7Ec9JNAzhS7mR_XlK" : {
    "Answer" : "so taht they acn't get caught in the shaft",
    "Question" : "Why are manhole covers round?"
  },
  "-JO7Eep6p6m2AXgwIvHj" : {
    "Answer" : "an art project?",
    "Question" : "What do you think this is?"
  },
  "-JO3dWgfL2PfpOaUvgfl" : {
    "Answer" : "$$$",
    "Question" : "How do you feel burdened?"
  },
  "-JO3d9AH3xqMSvz_cK73" : {
    "Answer" : "by any means necessary ",
    "Question" : "How often do you change your sheets?"
  },
  "-JO2eimc5cyFwjZOMsBm" : {
    "Answer" : "Nothing",
    "Question" : "What makes you feel optimistic?"
  },
  "-JO3aaOhxboRraBKD3Xl" : {
    "Answer" : "*txted",
    "Question" : "When was the last time you called them?"
  },
  "-JO7EZfatIYVlLE8oSAG" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you worry about your heroes?"
  },
  "-JO7Dhr0m2U7dCGDnrlF" : {
    "Answer" : "a fist punching a squinting face ",
    "Question" : "Describe what this looks like to you: (8>/--<"
  },
  "-JO7DsWIf4-PWi3tMd_Q" : {
    "Answer" : "a got an email soliciting some drawings for a online project",
    "Question" : "Describe the latest email or text message you've received."
  },
  "-JO7EYeQJk7YExvULear" : {
    "Answer" : "subalturn, but rich",
    "Question" : "In your next birth, you would love to be:"
  },
  "-JO3b9MmHeC7QnF7Y-lH" : {
    "Answer" : "it's beer",
    "Question" : "Describe something you like."
  },
  "-JO7E_dahh5sRJSMl3ly" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Have the implications of climate change ever kept you up at night?"
  },
  "-JO7DirWLZKpONZr3ehW" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Is your phone charged?"
  },
  "-JO3_dZiTxBbWq0E2D0I" : {
    "Answer" : "recently",
    "Question" : "When was the last time you went for a walk?"
  },
  "-JO3csa3nyPqhoPDIi5S" : {
    "Answer" : "VC",
    "Question" : "Would you identify as a hunter, gatherer, or other? If other, please specify."
  },
  "-JO7ETUdkf6wixT5buaQ" : {
    "Answer" : "maybe flashy",
    "Question" : "What would your ideal phone case look like?"
  },
  "-JO7DuycidKuu4oBJkUe" : {
    "Answer" : "inequality",
    "Question" : "What do you feel is the biggest problem in the world today?"
  },
  "-JO3cq5Q1goo_RBv6O-d" : {
    "Answer" : "Only before I bought an AC",
    "Question" : "Have the implications of climate change ever kept you up at night?"
  },
  "-JO7ENtUbYz6LXtKP9iR" : {
    "Answer" : "",
    "Question" : "Have you ever said a word and, immediately after, questioned whether it was actually a word at all?"
  },
  "-JO7EiKZMJg4UtSp0Kmo" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you use others' accounts on media streaming services?"
  },
  "-JO3_gqMTdWjp94mOxi7" : {
    "Answer" : "whenever ",
    "Question" : "How often do you express affection to loved ones?"
  },
  "-JO3dFu_znM0xRc0Ynwm" : {
    "Answer" : "how can one be Saussure?",
    "Question" : "Have you ever said a word and, immediately after, questioned whether it was actually a word at all?"
  },
  "-JO3c25lNThXObR5KRj6" : {
    "Answer" : "I don't recall ",
    "Question" : "Have you ever told someone \"not to take it out\" on you?"
  },
  "-JO7EInUI9Q41v32r1JK" : {
    "Answer" : "girlfriend. not sure about future. feel like maybe promising too mcuh",
    "Question" : "What concerns do you have in life that you would like to remedy? And what makes you feel that way?"
  },
  "-JO7ENrDXvIRlc7bG_LN" : {
    "Answer" : "lots of them",
    "Question" : "What conspiracy theories do you believe?"
  },
  "-JO3bLWzCG7Gf7_7IMMo" : {
    "Answer" : "an open space or enclosed field ",
    "Question" : "Would you rather be in an enclosed space or an open field?"
  },
  "-JO3clXG_1VX18fGVI_B" : {
    "Answer" : "<input type=\"text\">",
    "Question" : "What do you think this is?"
  },
  "-JO7Dw14qxFM6eEkmf-5" : {
    "Answer" : "",
    "Question" : "Are deadlines of relative, rather than absolute, importance to you?"
  },
  "-JO3_XH64bnDXI5MFiUq" : {
    "Answer" : "meh",
    "Question" : ""
  },
  "-JO3bsHB0jbpWubtXrNs" : {
    "Answer" : "no",
    "Question" : "Have you ever written a review on Yelp? If yes, why?"
  },
  "-JO7EvOTMKdy8HtQM5xo" : {
    "Answer" : "gatherer ",
    "Question" : "Would you identify as a hunter, gatherer, or other? If other, please specify."
  },
  "-JO3_f3jJhNaPaWmmfPM" : {
    "Answer" : "$$$",
    "Question" : "What makes you feel optimistic?"
  },
  "-JO3dO5-r3PiLiHs-EA3" : {
    "Answer" : "why are pipes round? ",
    "Question" : "Why are manhole covers round?"
  },
  "-JO7DmSC790hnq2C-KMT" : {
    "Answer" : "sex life",
    "Question" : "In what aspect of life do you feel the most compromised?"
  },
  "-JO3c9XYDQ-buFlajbx1" : {
    "Answer" : "Freud says neatness often hides repressed masturbatory urges ",
    "Question" : "Are your computer desktop and file system usually neat and orderly?"
  },
  "-JO7DdYP0dYubVVhkxkH" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy the outdoors?"
  },
  "-JO7EAsgnBUFjiGU8OFW" : {
    "Answer" : "depends",
    "Question" : "Would you rather be in an enclosed space or an open field?"
  },
  "-JO7EDsMVTeAJQiCiTXV" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Have you ever told someone \"not to take it out\" on you?"
  },
  "-JO3acOiXGI3bdj-oFoI" : {
    "Answer" : "of course not",
    "Question" : "Is your phone charged?"
  },
  "-JO3d6L03F2UyDwNKmrv" : {
    "Answer" : "n/a",
    "Question" : "Do you worry about your heroes?"
  },
  "-JO3cB4YFeaAZI7Ut7zw" : {
    "Answer" : "$$$",
    "Question" : "What worries people the most?"
  },
  "-JO3_aU_FFacRo_YOWGM" : {
    "Answer" : "sure",
    "Question" : "Do you feel secure?"
  },
  "-JO7DkBnflu81N5MSbA6" : {
    "Answer" : "yes",
    "Question" : "Do you spend a lot of your free time learning about things which have absolutely no practical application?"
  },
  "-JO3cQLN9xxJW5_fPniO" : {
    "Answer" : "southpaw ",
    "Question" : "Does your right hand look unusual now?"
  },
  "-JO7EC3rhY38z5zgW4Yr" : {
    "Answer" : "every day",
    "Question" : "Do you often think about humankind and its destiny?"
  },
  "-JO7ErI1d7FqPQ9H3FdF" : {
    "Answer" : "roles expected of me by my family and peers",
    "Question" : "How do you feel burdened?"
  },
  "-JO7DVNxazcJ4WmNAi3Z" : {
    "Answer" : "yesterday",
    "Question" : "When was the last time you went for a walk?"
  },
  "-JO7EQ-_pc9y3Ly-umTp" : {
    "Answer" : "thousands or millians",
    "Question" : "How many piano tuners are there in the entire world?"
  },
  "-JO3c_Qwn_Ox43YuNdoS" : {
    "Answer" : "no effort ",
    "Question" : "Do you make an effort to look smart?"
  },
  "-JO3aW6gkU6CwUmjmTfe" : {
    "Answer" : "rhizomatically ",
    "Question" : "Do you feel connected to the people around you?"
  },
  "-JO3aYBBDf9ybW3N7Te0" : {
    "Answer" : "...rhizomatically ",
    "Question" : "Do you enjoy being in large groups?"
  },
  "-JO3dV5Px4P652LyYP6-" : {
    "Answer" : "representations",
    "Question" : "Walking under the shade of an old oak tree, what do you see?"
  },
  "-JO7DZzQ7hJkKTDsoJig" : {
    "Answer" : "no",
    "Question" : "Do you feel connected to the people around you?"
  },
  "-JO3b0sMdvGlDY8KxP3x" : {
    "Answer" : "politically ",
    "Question" : "In what aspect of life do you feel the most compromised?"
  },
  "-JO7E4-YMlPotKT1VFAZ" : {
    "Answer" : "status\n",
    "Question" : "What worries people the most?"
  },
  "-JO3cw5CJLOd-4wMR4BL" : {
    "Answer" : "no; constant ",
    "Question" : "Do you worry about the NSA reading your email? If yes, how frequent is your worry?"
  },
  "-JO3bGqKTU2Bm5rUrPZq" : {
    "Answer" : "Only on Mondays",
    "Question" : "Do you often think about humankind and its destiny?"
  },
  "-JO7EgHEIdCQV5wSSOYE" : {
    "Answer" : "no",
    "Question" : "Is time running out, slowing down, or changed completely?"
  },
  "-JO7E-XnN2sawSRinVGE" : {
    "Answer" : "?",
    "Question" : "When was the last time you called them?"
  },
  "-JO2eauSQJ5Ih1YyqRn7" : {
    "Answer" : "So so",
    "Question" : ""
  },
  "-JO7EjTbwqUB7Tz_rv4i" : {
    "Answer" : "vastly",
    "Question" : "To what degree do you think your local geography influences your aesthetic preferences?"
  },
  "-JO3asPZto3qnDTeiSLH" : {
    "Answer" : "death; dying ",
    "Question" : "What concerns do you have in life that you would like to remedy? And what makes you feel that way?"
  }
}
